# **BO BARTOLOME**

bobartolome@gmail.com | 808-264-0391 | bobartolome.com | github.com/operator130

#### **ABOUT**

Professional with 8+ years of experience committing to the highest standards of customer service in a tourism focused industry. Proven to be reliable, technically proficient in the use of technology, adaptable to change, and focused on details.

## **SKILLS**

- Knowledgeable in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with additional experience in Node.js, Express, and MongoDB
- Proficient in Windows OS, Mac OS, and Microsoft Office Suite

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Federal Aviation Administration**

Air Traffic Control Trainee

Oklahoma City, OK Dec 2021 - Apr 2022

- Promoted the safe, orderly, and expeditious flow of air traffic in a simulated environment
- Memorized and implemented all Standard Operating Procedures and Letters of Agreements in accordance with the Federal Aviation Administration
- Interpreted flight plans and adjusted priorities as needed

#### **Marriott International**

Guest Service Representative

Kahului, HI

Dec 2018 - Mar 2021

- Exercised impeccable customer service to current and future guests
- Organized, confirmed, and processed guest check-ins and check-outs
- Secured payment while verifying and adjusting financial transactions
- Ran daily reports and audited discrepancies within the Property Management System

### **Marriott Vacations Worldwide**

Loss Prevention Officer/Dispatcher

Lahaina, HI

Jan 2014 - Dec 2018

- Specialized in dispatching officers and associates to assignments
- Proactively looked for and solved issues relating to accidents, injuries, and unsafe work conditions
- Developed, implemented, and monitored corrective measures
- Protected company assets and maintained confidentiality of proprietary information
- Documented and filed incident reports
- Provided coverage as a Manager on Duty

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Hawaii at Manoa

Communications

Honolulu, HI

Aug 2007 - Dec 2012

Kamehameha Schools Maui Campus

High School Diploma

Makawao, HI

Aug 2004 - May 2007